Andrew D'Angelo

Present Address 4000 NE 15th Avenue Seattle, WA 98195 Permanent Address 1310 Maple Avenue Wilmette, IL 60091 Contact Information
dangeloandrew@outlook.com
+1 (847) 906-3448
GitHub Profile
https://github.com/excelangue

Summary

A dedicated and creative student with a strong mathematical background who wants to leverage both self-taught and formal experience designing and writing computer software. Able to design architectures and algorithms at a high level and then implement solutions at a lower level in any of a multitude of languages and frameworks.

Education

Undergraduate, University of Washington, Seattle, WA

2014-Present

- Currently a junior studying Computer Science and Applied Mathematics
- 2014–2015 school year: Dean's List with 3.8 GPA

Student, New Trier High School, Winnetka, IL

2010-2014

- 4.4 weighted GPA, 36 ACT
- Presidential Scholar semifinalist
- Member of the German National Honor Society

Computer Skills

Software: Windows, Windows Server 2012, OS X, Linux sys-

tem administration, primarily Arch and Debian

Languages: C for PC and Game Boy Advance, Python with

Django and Web2Py, Java, C# and F# for the .NET framework, LISP. Current focus on machine

learning and biological simulation in F#

Work Experience

Software Engineering Intern, Quicket Solutions, Champaign, IL Summer 2015

- Wrote and maintained database interface and backend management Python and Web2Py code creating a complete electronic police citation management service.
- Experienced designing and implementing software solutions in a tight-knit, collaborative group and planning extensible and robust systems for data processing in a fast moving startup environment.

Technical Consultant, Panorama Innovation, Wilmette, IL Jun. 2014–Sept. 2014

• Research, system design & software implementation for retail intelligence systems using OpenWRT on commodity access points for data collection and Python for data processing and analytics.

IT Technician, Unite Here Health, Chicago, IL

Jul. 2014-Aug. 2014

• Computer system set-up and maintenance for health insurance events. Responsibilities included wired and wireless network configuration, cabling, Windows networking, and troubleshooting.

Published two apps to the Windows Phone store

May 2014

- Thorntons++: a customer loyalty and coupon app for a gas station chain.
- Omeddle: an Omegle chat client with the additional ability to intercept and modify messages sent between other Omegle users. Peaked at 2,000 downloads a month, won 3rd place at the 2014 Microsoft //publish/ event in the Chicago app competition.